syberplace.com 2010-09-22

# Privacy

  * Personal Information
  * Surveys and Competitions
  * Partnerships
  * Changes
  * External Links
  * How to contact SyberPlace about this privacy policy?

SyberPlace privacy policy for the internet.

**Personal Information**

SyberPlace respects your privacy on the Internet. Whenever and wherever possible, SyberPlace will treat the information about you received on the Internet with utmost care and confidentiality. SyberPlace uses information provided by you to measure the use of our site and to improve its content. We may use this information to respond to your requests, or to contact you to advise of new products, services or promotions via post, e-mail or phone. If you place an order for a product, request a service or submit content to this site, we may need to contact you for additional information. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways not specified or disclosed in this statement. The personal information we collect is used only to respond to your enquiry, process an order or allow you to access specific account information. At times, cookies may be used to provide you with certain information. A cookie is a tiny element of data that a Website can send to your browser. It may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Top

**Surveys and Competitions**

From time to time, our site may request information from users via surveys or competitions. Participation in these surveys or competitions is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address) and demographic information (such as gender, age). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and to award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the functionality and user satisfaction of this site. We do not share aggregated demographic information with our partners or advertisers. Top

**Partnerships**

The products and services that we provide are rendered in collaboration with branded original equipment manufacturers and reputed service providers. We will share names, or other contact information that will be necessary for our partners to fulfill orders and provide services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. Top

**Changes**

We may change this Privacy Policy, or change, modify or withdraw access to this site or the content of these pages at any time with or without notice. Top

**External Links**

SyberPlace.com contains links to other sites, whilst we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and our respect for privacy, we cannot be responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites. Top

**How to contact SyberPlace about this privacy policy?**

It is important to us at SyberPlace to hear what visitors have to say about our services, and our policies. If site visitors have any questions, concerns, or complaints about this Privacy Policy, or want to let us know what they think about SyberPlace.com or the products and services that we offer, they can send us an email at [admin@syberplace.com.](mailto:admin@syberplace.com?subject=Contact%20Us-Privacy) Top
